Please sit in the waiting room over there, Mrs. Iwakura.
So... Ms. Iwakura, please wait there in the waiting room.
Lain, there's no need to be worried.
Lain, n-ai de ce să te îngrijorez.
Come, take a seat over here.
Te rog să te așezi acolo.
Ah... would you like a juice or something to drink?
Ah... vrei un suc sau ceva de băut?
If you don't, that's fine as well.
E ok dacă nu vrei. Nu te îngrijora.
Let me see...
Umm...
I'm thirsty, so I'll probably make some black tea. Would you like to join me, Lain?
Mi-e cam sete, mă duc să beau un ceai... Vrei să vii și tu?
It'd be odd if I was the only one with a drink, right?
Pentru că e cam ciudat dacă doar eu beau.
Thank you.
Mulțumesc.
What would you like?
Pe care o vrei?
I have all kinds of drinks.
Avem de ales.
Whatever you're having.
La fel și ție.
You want tea as well?
Ceai negru?
Wonderful!
Hai să-l i-au pe ăsta.
Give me just a moment...
Stai un pic...
You can add sugar and milk as well, if you'd like.
Poți să pui zahăr și lapte în el dacă dorești.
Here.
Poftim!
Not bad, huh?
Not bad, huh?
Earl Gray - it's one of my favorites.
Ceai Earl Grey, chiar îmi place ăsta.
Earl Grey?
Earl Grey?
Right.
Da!
There are many different types of tea, all with different smells and tastes.
Există varietate și în ceaiurile negre, cu diferite arome și miresme.
Is it good?
Are un gust bun?
Well...
Păi...
I think it's very good,
Este bun pentru mine.
but I don't know what your taste is like.
Dar nu sunt sigură dacă îți va place, Lain.
Drink a little bit and see if you like it.
Dacă vrei, poți să bei un pic.
If it doesn't taste good, we can always make you something else, right?
Dacă nu e pentru gusturile tale, putem să facem alt ceva.
Here you go.
Uite...